var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "India",
        options : [
            "USA",
            "England",
            "India",
            "Pakistan",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Butan",
    options : [
        "Butan",
        "Indonesia",
        "Bangladesh",
        "Brazil",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "North Korea",
    options : [
        "Canada",
        "Belize",
        "China",
        "North Korea",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Ukraine",
    options : [
        "Fiji",
        "Iran",
        "Jordan",
        "Ukraine",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "France",
    options : [
        "France",
        "Haiti",
        "Holy See",
        "Greece",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Japan",
    options : [
        "Kiribati",
        "Liberia",
        "Japan",
        "Mali",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "China",
    options : [
        "Niger",
        "China",
        "Norway",
        "Morocco",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "Sri Lanka",
    options : [
        "Togo",
        "Sri Lanka",
        "Uganda",
        "Syria",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "South Africa",
    options : [
        "Spain",
        "Liberia",
        "Poland",
        "South Africa",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Russia",
    options : [
        "Russia",
        "Saudi Arabia",
        "Spain",
        "Mali",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Pakistan",
    options : [
        "Kiribati",
        "Pakistan",
        "Syria",
        "Tajikistan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "New Zealand",
    options : [
        "New Zealand",
        "Morocco",
        "Namibia",
        "Norway",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Brazil",
    options : [
        "Australia",
        "Cyprus",
        "Germany",
        "Brazil",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "Iceland",
    options : [
        "Iceland",
        "Jamaica",
        "Malawi",
        "Hungary",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Mexico",
    options : [
        "Mexico",
        "Hungary",
        "Iran",
        "Jordan",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Netherlands",
    options : [
        "Latvia",
        "Netherlands",
        "Mongolia",
        "Greece",
    ]
},
{
    num : 17,
    question : "",
    answer : "Bangladesh",
    options : [
        "Iran",
        "Haiti",
        "Bangladesh",
        "Estonia",
    ]
},
{
    num : 18,
    question : "",
    answer : "Indonesia",
    options : [
        "Indonesia",
        "Andorra",
        "Cuba",
        "Egypt",
    ]
},
{
    num : 19,
    question : "",
    answer : "Iran",
    options : [
        "Germany",
        "Italy",
        "Kazakhstan",
        "Iran",
    ]
},
{
    num : 20,
    question : "",
    answer : "South Korea",
    options : [
        "Norway",
        "South Korea",
        "Japan",
        "Poland",
    ]
},
{
    num : 21,
    question : "",
    answer : "England",
    options : [
        "Rwanda",
        "Morocco",
        "England",
        "Norway",
    ]
}

];